xray-mag.com 2019-06-06

# Privacy Policy & GDPR compliance | X-Ray Mag

On 25 May, 2018, the European Union's General Data Protection Regulation, commonly called GDPR, became not only the law of the land in Europe but has global implications. GDPR is a regulation that requires businesses to protect the personal data and privacy of EU citizens for transactions that occur within EU member states.

This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for [www.xray-mag.com](http://www.xray-mag.com/). This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:

  * What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared. 
  * What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data. 
  * The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information. 
  * How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information. 

### Information Collection, Use, and Sharing

AquaScope Media Aps is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.

We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, and to send out newsletters and notifications about new issues being published.

Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.

### Your Access to and Control Over Information

You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:

  * See what data we have about you, if any. 
  * Change/correct any data we have about you.
  * Have us delete any data we have about you.
  * Express any concern you have about our use of your data.

### Security

We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.

Wherever we handle sensitive information such as credit card data, that information is handled by a third parties such as banks and credit card terminal providers. All information transmitted in such transactions are handled by us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page.

While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, responding to inquiries from readers or customers, maintenance of our subscriber database or billing of clients) are granted access to personally identifiable information, and only on a need to see basis. 

The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment. Credit card companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes beyond filling your order.

### Cookies

We use "cookies" on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor's hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site.

Currently the website only sets the cookies required for it to function properly. These cookies are not seen or used by any human or shared.

#### Performance cookies

Google Analytics is used to monitor performance. Data collection for advertising features has been switched OFF and IP addresses of hits sent to Google Analytics has been anonymized.

#### Advertisers and marketeers' cookies

There aren't any. All banner advertising is hosted and managed internally. We do currently not work with any outside 3rd party solution providers in these regards.

#### Social media cookies

Our site displays social media plugins such as buttons for sharing news on Twitter and Facebook and for posting comments on Facebook. However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.

### Links

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.

### Surveys & Contests

From time-to-time our site requests information via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you may choose whether or not to participate and therefore disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.

### Updates

Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time and all updates will be posted on this page.

If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via via email using the contact form on our contact page.
